Gross, Robert; Papers apap291
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Lighting the Torch of Conscience, 1986-1992; 4; 1.0 cubic ft.
  - Catholic Bishops, 1987; Undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Catholic Orders, 1989-1990; Undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Christian Church Disciples, Undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Christian Peacemaker Teams, 1989; Undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Church of the Brethren, 1989-1990; Undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Community Liaison Project, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Concept of Pledges, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Coordinator Recruitment- Network, 1986; 1989; Undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Coordinator Recruitment- State, 1988-1990; Undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Coordinators, State Mailings to, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Database Printout, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Descriptive, 1989; Undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Direct Action- Christmas Tree, 1989; Undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Financial Records, 1988-1990; Undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Financial Report, 1989-1990; Undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Finances- Bank Statements, 1989-1990; Undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Florida Impact, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - For LTC- SC Meeting, Undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Fundraising, 1989-1990; Undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Hutterian Brethren, 1988-1990 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Invoices, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - LTC- March Orders, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - LTC- Orders Filled, 1989; Undated (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Manchester College, 1989; Undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Media and Publicity, 1988-1990; Undated (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - National Interreligious Task Force on Criminal Justice, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - National Religious Bodies, 1989; Undated (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - NCADP Resource List, Undated (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - News Sheet, 1989-1990; Undated (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1990; Undated (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Orders Filled in 1991, 1989-1991; Undated (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Orders Filled- February 28, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Orders Sent in April, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Orders Sent in December, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Orders Sent in February, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Orders Sent in January, 1989-1990; Undated (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Orders Sent in May, 1989-1990; Undated (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Orders Sent in November, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Organizational Participation, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Outreach and Lists, 1988-1989; Undated (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Packet Contents, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Packet Cover Letter, Undated (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Participating Organizations, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - PAX Christi, 1989; Undated (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Pilgrimage, 1990; Undated (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Pilgrimage- Evaluations, 1989-1992; Undated (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Pilgrimage- Materials and Master Copies, 1990; Undated (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Pilgrimage- Materials and Master Copies, LTC Files (1 of 2), Undated (Floppy-disk 1)
  - Pilgrimage- Materials and Master Copies, LTC Files (2 of 2), Undated (Floppy-disk 2)
  - Pilgrimage- Minutes and Meeting Notes, 1989-1990; Undated (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Pilgrimage- The Next, 1990; Undated (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Pilgrimage- Notes From Dr. Folks, 1990; Undated (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Pilgrimage- Photos, 1990; Undated (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Pilgrimage- Pilgrims By State (1 of 2), 1990; Undated (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Pilgrimage- Pilgrims By State (2 of 2), 1990; Undated (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Pledges, By Faith Group, Undated (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Presbyterians, 1989-1990; Undated (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Presentations, 1989; Undated (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Pre-South Carolina Planning, 1988-1989; Undated (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Program Ideas, Undated (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Program Planning, 1988-1989; Undated (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Reformed Church, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Reports, 1989; Undated (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Resource Materials- Ideas, 1988-1989; Undated (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Resource Materials- In Progress, 1989-1990; Undated (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Resources- Master Copies, 1987; 1989 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Sermons, Undated (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Service Guidelines, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Sisters of Mercy, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Sisters of St. Joseph, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Spanish Translation, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Speakers Bureau, 1989; Undated (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - State Coordinators Guidelines, 1989; Undated (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - State Coordinators Packet Cover Letter, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - State Level Pilgrimages, Undated (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Statement, 1988-1989; Undated (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Steering Committee, 1989-1990; Undated (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - Study Resources- Capital Punishment, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - Summit- Meeting, 1988-1989; Undated (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - Summit- Parallel Events, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - Support Guidelines, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - Swedenborgian Church, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - Taking the Torch to a Meeting, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 90)
  - Timeline, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 91)
  - Torch Artwork, 1989; Undated (Box 1, Folder 92)
  - United Methodists, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 93)
  - Videotapes, 1989-1990; Undated (Box 1, Folder 94)
  - Witness Guidelines, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 95)